Guide to the Hugh R. Pomeroy papers, 1926-1970
Pomeroy, Hugh R. papers, 1926-1970
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Hugh R. Pomeroy papers, 1926-1970.
3961
Hugh R.(Hugh Reynolds), Pomeroy 1899-1961.
.8 cubic ft.
Manuscript drafts; mimeographed and printed papers, talks, and addresses; an outline; transcripts; photographs; and other materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Manuscript drafts; mimeographed and printed papers, talks, and addresses; outline of a seminar series at the University of North Carolina; transcripts of testimony as an expert witness; printed material relating to zoning; correspondence; and other materials about Pomeroy. Also, two photographs.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Hugh Pomeroy (1899-1961) served as Executive Director, American Society of Planning Officials, director of the Los Angeles County Regional Planning Commission, and director of the Westchester County Department of Planning and was a member of the International Fraternity of Lambda Alpha.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Manuscript drafts; mimeographed and printed papers, talks, and addresses; outline of a seminar series at the University of North Carolina; transcripts of testimony as an expert witness; printed material relating to zoning; correspondence; and other materials about Pomeroy. Also, two photographs.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Pomeroy, Hugh R.1899-1961.; Lambda Alpha International.
Subjects:
City planning.; Regional planning.; Zoning.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Part of Lambda Alpha Literary Archives.
CONTAINER LIST
- Manuscript drafts of papers, talks, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Manuscript drafts of papers, talks, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Manuscript drafts of papers, talks, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Manuscript drafts of papers, talks, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Manuscript drafts of papers, talks, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Manuscript drafts of papers, talks, 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Manuscript drafts of papers, talks, 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Mimeographed and printed papers, talks, statements, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Mimeographed and printed papers, talks, statements, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Mimeographed and printed papers, talks, statements, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Mimeographed and printed papers, talks, statements, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Mimeographed and printed papers, talks, statements, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Mimeographed and printed papers, talks, statements, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Mimeographed and printed papers, talks, statements, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Mimeographed and printed papers, talks, statements, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Mimeographed and printed papers, talks, statements, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Typescript (carbon) talks, lecture, papers, reports, 1950-1960 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- "Planning the World in a Skyscraper", 1947 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Schedule-outline of seminar series, University of North Carolina, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Robert M. Leary correspondence, 1956-1960 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Statement at public hearing, Montgomery County, Maryland, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- City of Ann Arbor v. Northwest Park Construction Corporation; Pomeroy as Expert Witness, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Wiltwyck v. Perry; Pomeroy as Expert Witness, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Transcript of speech--Fall Conference of the Organization of Cornell Planners, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Articles, reprints by and about Pomeroy, 1926-1961 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Printed material: The Sub-division of Land in San Mateo County, California, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Printed material: Herman W. Fischer vs. Township of Bedminster, New Jersey, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Printed material: A Planning Manual for Zoning, preliminary draft by Pomeroy, American Society of Planning Officials, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Printed material: A Planning Manual for Zoning, vol. II, by Pomeroy, American Society of Planning Officials, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Photographs (2) of Pomeroy (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Other material concerning Pomeroy, 1950-1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)